born-unique.com 2015-09-06

# Privacy | The Born Unique Baby Guide

### Privacy Policy & FTC Disclaimer

  1. Product disclosure: YOUR Virtual Service Group sells products, is an affiliate for products listed on this website, and earns a commission based on any sales referred.
  2. Introduction: Baby Guide Born Unique (this website) is owned and managed by YOUR Virtual Service Group (we, us, our). We respect the privacy of our website visitors (you, your). This privacy policy explains how we may collect, use, disclose, and store your personal information as provided to us. By visiting and using this website you provide your unconditional consent to us collecting, using, disclosing, and storing your personal information as described in this privacy policy.
  3. Terms of use: Our terms of use govern your use of this website, this privacy policy must be read in conjunction with our terms of use.
  4. Collecting your personal information: We may collect your personal information (including, without limitation, your name, email address, phone number, and postal address) when you use this website. You have the power to decide not to provide your personal information to us. However, if you decide not to provide it, then we may be unable to provide you with access to specific features, information, or products.
  5. Automated collection: When you visit this website, we may use automated methods and tools (such as sessions, cookies, and software that monitors usage) to collect information about your visit (without limitation). The information described will be used in aggregate form to analyze how the website is being used by visitors (for example: to analyze usage patterns in order to make website improvements). Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not disclose any information except in aggregate form.
  6. Cookies: This website may use sessions and cookies in order to provide you with specific functionality or services. This technology is used to, amongst other things, identify you as an individual visitor of this website. Accepting a cookie will not give us access to any data on your computer other than the data stored in the cookie. Although you may configure your web browser to not accept cookies, as a result you may experience a loss of website functionality.
  7. Additional collection: If we are concerned about website security breaches or patterns of abnormal website usage, then we may gather more extensive information.
  8. Use: We may use your personal information to: provide you with requested information and services; provide important service and website information and notifications; provide other information (including news, promotional material, and event information) where you agree to receive it; verify your identity and to assist you in recovering forgotten username or password information; update or improve products or this website; respond to your communications and initiate communication; and personalize the website according to your preferences.
  9. Other use and disclosure: We will not sell, lease, or rent your personal information to any third party. We may disclose your personal information only to our professional advisors, contractors, business associates, and related companies who have agreed to this privacy policy regarding the treatment of your personal information. We will not otherwise disclose or use your personal information except: for any purpose described in clause 6; where you have authorized us to do so; where we have provided notification of the intended disclosure or use and you have not objected to it; where we believe that disclosure or use is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement or national security agency in the performance of their functions; where we believe that such disclosure or use is reasonably necessary to enforce legal rights we may have, or is reasonably necessary to protect the property, rights, and safety of our visitors, us, or others; or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
  10. Third party websites: This website may contain hyperlinks to websites owned and managed by third parties. We are not responsible for the manner in which those websites collect, store, use, and distribute personal information you provide or the content of such websites. When you visit a third party website via a hyperlink displayed on this website, we encourage you to review that website’s privacy policy and disclosure so that you can understand how your personal information may be collected, stored, used and distributed by that entity.
  11. Right to access and request correction: It is important to us that the personal information we obtain from you is accurate, updated, and complete. If you would like your personal information corrected or updated, or simply desire access to your personal information, then please contact our Privacy Officer in order to request access to your personal information that we (or our contractors) hold. When you make any such request: we may ask you to put your request in writing; in some circumstances permitted by law, we may not provide such information to you (and we may not be able to require our contractors to provide such information to you); if we decide not to correct or provide you with access to your personal information, we will give you the reasons for our decision; when we provide the requested information or carry out the requested correction (or where we attach to that information a statement of any correction sought but not made), we may require you to pay a reasonable fee determined by us.
  12. Changes to our privacy policy: We reserve the right to change the privacy policy from time to time by publishing the revised privacy policy on our website. If you continue to use this website or provide personal information after we post changes to this privacy policy, this will confirm your conclusive acceptance of such changes.
